Finding Aid for Engineering Communications & Marketing (University of Michigan) records 1860-2010
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan 1998
Engineering Communications & Marketing (University of Michigan) records
1860-2010
1960-2000
University of Michigan. Engineering Communications & Marketing.
9683 Bimu C146 2
Unit of the University of Michigan College of Engineering responsible for producing print and multi-media publications for the college. Records include administrative files and publications, photographs, videotapes, and other material produced for internal and external use to document and illustrate research, faculty, staff, students and alumni of the College of Engineering.
33.5 linear feet
1 oversize folders
1 oversize volumes
Bentley Historical Library University of Michigan
The records were transferred from the College of Engineering Office of Communications & Marketing (donor no. 8405 ) beginning in September 1995. An additional 23 boxes were received in 2010.
Periodic additions to the records are expected.
The collection is open for research.
The University of Michigan College of Engineering Office of Communications & Marketing serves as an editorial and production office for College of Engineering publications, outreach efforts, special events, and alumni and development activities. Staff members coordinate the production of publications and online content, including research, writing, editing and design. The antecedents of the Office of Communications & Marketing can be traced back several decades to the 1950s when the College of Engineering began publishing a newsletter for engineering alumni. Under the deanship of Gordon J. Van Wylen (1965-1972) the dean's newsletter evolved into several publications, the bulletins Ingenor and Technium and a newsletter which appeared under various names, News, Newsletter, and Newsliner.
In 1990, Interim Dean Daniel Atkins hired permanent staff for the publication effort. Dean Peter Banks moved publications to the College Relations area under Terry Wood, then Assistant Dean and Director of College Relations. In 1993, Brad Canale assumed the position of Executive Director of College Relations with Engineering Communications as a part of that office. In 2011 the College underwent a reorganization and Engineering Communications, now known as Communications and Marketing, became the Office of Communications & Marketing with the Executive Director reporting directly to the Dean of the College and becoming a member of the Dean's Cabinet.
Since 1990, the Office of Communications & Marketing has been responsible for a wide assortment of regular and special print publications and functions. The unit also produces scripts for special events such as commencement, dedications, and award ceremonies. Due to its connection with alumni and development activities, the office has served as an unofficial repository for historical material collected from throughout the engineering campus as well as from alumni.
The record group Engineering Communications & Marketing contains records documenting the history of the University of Michigan College of Engineering, particularly the photographic history of the college. Documentation includes memos, correspondence, written scripts for special events, photographs, slides, contact sheets, negatives, one cassette recording and one compact disc. The record group is divided into five series that reflect the Office's original filing arrangement: Historical, Office Files, Coded Files, Visual Materials, and Faculty Background Files.
Subjects:
University of Michigan. Engineering Communications.; University of Michigan. College of Engineering.; North Campus (University of Michigan)
Subjects - Visual Material:
Cooley, Mortimer E., 1855-1946.; Camp Davis (University of Michigan); Quarterdeck Society (University of Michigan); University of Michigan--Buildings.; University of Michigan. Engineering Communications.; University of Michigan. College of Engineering.; North Campus (University of Michigan); World War, 1914-1918--Michigan--Ann Arbor.
Genre/Form:
Photographs.
- Historical, 1894-1995
  The Historical series (1894-1995, 1 linear foot) consists of a miscellaneous assemblage of correspondence, reports and student memorabilia documenting the history of the College of Engineering. Research files include information on early women graduates and a survey of historical artifacts within the College of Engineering. The Engineering Communications & Marketing office compiled this material primarily for use in publications and at reunions. Several of the items were donated by engineering alumni and class officers.
  - Welding Tests, 1894 (Box 1)
  - Class of 1904 minutes, 1902-1909 (Box 1)
  - Class of 1913 Student Campaign Cards (Box 1)
  - Manual of Foundry Principles and Practice, 1922 (Box 1)
    (with student notes)
  - Degrees Granted in Engineering; Historical and Statistical Information, circa 1930-1960 (Box 1)
  - Aeronautical Engineering; Historical Documents and Clippings, 1930-1958 (Box 1)
  - Summary of Enrollment 1903-1934 compiled circa 1934 (Box 1)
  - Historical Documents, 1928-1966 (Box 1)
  - Student Documents of Carl Seasword, 1931 (Box 1)
  - Engineering Open House, circa 1928-1965 (Box 1)
  - Class of 1917 Reunion Material, 1937-1967 (Box 1)
  - Mortimer Cooley Foundation, 1938 (Box 1)
  - Student "Key" (George Hogg), 1938 (Box 1)
  - Defense Program, 1940-1941 (Box 1)
  - Study of Enrollment, circa 1945-1956 (Box 1)
  - Guest Book, 1953-1972 (Box 1)
  - William Stirton Correspondence, 1956-1960 (Box 1)
  - Clippings re: Minorities at College of Engineering, 1960-1970 (Box 1)
  - Faculty Handbook, 1961-1962 (Box 1)
  - Axel Marin (Tau Beta Pi), 1961 (Box 1)
  - Historical Material, 1909-1990; 2 folders (Box 1)
  - Department of Industrial Engineering, 1969 (Box 1)
  - Metallurgical Engineering Report, 1969 (Box 1)
  - Engineering Publications Office, 1969-1982; undated; 2 folders (Box 1)
  - Report of Study and Recommendations for a Capital Gifts Campaign, 1972 (Box 1)
  - Capital Campaign Mailings, 1973-1976 (Box 1)
  - Degree Statistics 1845-1985 compiled 1981-1987, 1845-1987 (Box 1)
  - Report on Graduation Rates in College of Engineering, undated (Box 1)
  - Early History of the College of Engineering, undated (Box 1)
  - Women Engineers (includes first women graduates), 1994 (Box 1)
  - Historical Artifacts Survey, 1995 (Box 1)
- Office Files, 1978-1997
  The Office Files (1978-1997, 1.2 linear feet) series consists of correspondence, reports, and memos concerning the typical activities of the Office of Communications & Marketing. The series documents alumni activities, building dedications, commencement, fundraising, and other activities. It is organized alphabetically. Building dedications and groundbreakings include the Herbert H. Dow Building, Electrical Engineering and Computer Science (EECS) Building, Lurie Bell Tower, and Lurie Engineering Center.
  - Aerospace Engineering 75th Anniversary, 1989 (Box 2)
  - Alumni Society Meetings, 1989; 2 folders (Box 2)
  - Commencement, 1983-1991; 9 folders (Box 2)
  - Davis Memorial Plaque Information, 1996 (Box 2)
  - Dedications and Groundbreakings
    - Naval Architecture and Marine Engineering Building Dedication, 1978 (Box 2)
    - Herbert H. Dow Building
      - Groundbreaking, 1980 (Box 2)
      - Dedication, 1983 (Box 2)
    - Electrical Engineering and Computer Science Building
      - Groundbreaking, 1984; 2 folders (Box 2)
      - Dedication, 1986-1987; 2 folders (Box 2)
      - Audio Cassette of Dedication Speech, 1986 (Box 2)
    - Solid State Laboratory Dedication, 1987 (Box 2)
    - Space Physics Research Center Dedication, 1987 (Box 2)
    - Optical Sciences Laboratory Dedication, 1989 (Box 2)
    - Francois-Xavier Bagnoud Building Dedication, 1993 (Box 2)
    - Integrated Technology Instructional Center, Groundbreaking, 1994 (Box 2)
    - "The Wave Field," Sculpture by Maya Lin, Installation outside Francois-Xavier Bagnoud Building, 1995 (Box 2)
    - Lurie Building
      - Dedication Ceremony, 1996 (Box 2)
      - Yuan Screen, Installation in Lurie Center, 1996 (Box 2)
      - Installation of Bells in Lurie Tower, 1996 (Box 2)
      - Compact Disc-"True Blue" by Chip Davis, Dedication Piece for Lurie Tower, 1996 (Box 2)
  - Dean Steven Director, Speeches and Correspondence, 1996-1997 (Box 2)
  - Inauguration of James J. Duderstadt, 1988 (Box 2)
  - Robert and Ann Lurie, 1985-1995; 2 folders (Box 2)
  - Meeting Agendas, 1997 (Box 3)
  - Martin Luther King Day, 1990-1994 (Box 3)
  - National Advisory Committee, 1983-1989; 7 folders (Box 3)
  - Riggs Fellowship, 1978-1984 (Box 3)
  - Shien-Ming Wu Memorial, 1993 (Box 3)
  - Tauber Manufacturing Institute-Public Relations, 1996 (Box 3)
- Coded Files
  Coded Files (1860-1994, 5 linear feet) retains the original color-coded filing scheme used by the Office of Communications & Marketing. The series is divided into subseries based on the color-code. Records include scripts, photographic material, reports, and newspaper articles. The first subseries, "Scripts," (1990-1993, 0.8 linear foot) contains written scripts for events and video productions such as the Francois-Xavier Bagnoud Building dedication, and the memorial for professor Shien-Ming Wu. The second subseries, "Buildings, Construction and Landscaping," (yellow dot) (1985-1991, 0.4 linear foot) contains photographs, slides, contact sheets, and negatives. The third subseries, "Computers Laboratories and Facilities" (blue dot) (1983-1993, 0.2 linear foot) consists of photographs, slides, contact sheets. The fourth and fifth subseries "Events" (orange dot) (1985-1993 0.8 linear foot) and "People" (red dot) (1968-1993, 1.0 linear foot) contain photographs, slides, contact sheets, and negatives. The subseries of "Miscellaneous coded material" (1987-1994, 0.2 linear foot) consists of three bound publications: "A Survey of Intellectual Activities," 1987, "Briefing for Regent Veronica L. Smith," 1988, and newspaper and magazine clippings about the University of Michigan College of Engineering, 1993-1994. The subseries, "Various Photographs and Slides" (purple dot) (1860-1993, 2.3 linear feet) contains topically arranged photographs coded with a purple dot and the subseries "Various Brochures and Programs" (green dot) (1987-1995, .5 linear feet) contains pamphlets, programs and photographs from different events coded with a green dot. Because the two subseries were accessioned later than the rest of the coded files, they are physically separate from the rest of the coded files.
  - Scripts, 1990-1993
    - Alumni Society Annual Meeting, 1993 (Box 3)
    - Alumni Society Awards Dinner, 1993 (Box 3)
    - Alumni Society Board/Annual Meetings, 1993 (Box 3)
    - Amoco Dedication, December 2, 1992 (Box 3)
    - Class Rep. Workshop, May 8, 1993 (Box 3)
    - Endowed Professors Dinner, May 1, 1992 (Box 3)
    - Endowed Professorship Dinner, April 30, 1993 (Box 3)
    - Emeritus Engineering Luncheon, June 4, 1993 (Box 3)
    - Francois-Xavier Bagnoud (FXB) Aerospace Prize, October, 1993 (Box 3)
    - Francois-Xavier Bagnoud (FXB) Building Dedication and Luncheon Celebration, October 8, 1993 (Box 3)
    - Gala, Design for Impact Campaign Kickoff, September 17, 1992 (Box 3)
    - Historical Video Script, Dwight Stevenson, 1990 (Box 3)
    - NEO Video Script, 1992 (Box 3)
    - New Faculty Script, 1993 (Box 3)
    - "Solar Car" Video Script, 1990 (Box 3)
    - Tenure Script, 1993 (Box 3)
    - Shien-Ming Wu Memorial Script, April 17, 1993 (Box 3)
  - Buildings, Construction, and Landscaping Photographs, Slides, Contact Sheets, and Negatives (yellow dot), 1985-1991
    - Anvil Office, June 21, 1988 (Box 3)
    - Central Campus, Senior Class Benches and Plaques, March, 1987 (Box 3)
    - Center for Display Technology and Manufacturing (Box 3)
    - Chrysler Center for Continuing Education (Box 3)
    - Cooley Building (Box 3)
    - Dow Library, June 20, 1991 (Box 3)
    - Dow Lounge, June 21, 1988 (Box 3)
    - Electrical Engineering and Computer Science (EECS)
      - Architectural Renderings (Box 3)
      - Atrium, June 21, 1988 (Box 3)
      - Atrium, February 3, 1988 (Box 3)
      - Atrium, K. Mead, 1990 (Box 3)
      - Building Construction, April 1985 (Box 3)
      - Building, October 28, 1986 (Box 3)
      - Building, November 1986 (Box 3)
      - Building, Jim Beck, Development and Marketing Communication (DMC), Spring 1988 (Box 3)
    - Francois-Xavier Bagnoud Building (Box 3)
    - Industrial and Operations Engineering Building, undated (Box 3)
    - Lay Auto Laboratory, undated (Box 3)
    - Lurie Engineering Center (Box 3)
    - Lurie Tower (Box 3)
    - Naval Architecture (Box 3)
    - North Campus
      - Aerial View, March 10, 1988 (Box 3)
      - Building Scenes, November 15, 1987 (Box 3)
      - Building Scenes, Misc. Interior and Exterior, undated (Box 3)
    - Space Research Lab, undated (Box 3)
  - Computers and Facilities Photographs, Slides, Contact Sheets, and Negatives (blue dot), 1983-1993
    - Apollo Computers, 1983-1987 (Box 3)
    - Computer Aided Engineering Network (CAEN) Apollo Laboratory (Box 3)
    - Civil Laboratory Students, June 23, 1986 (Box 3)
    - Computer Shots, 1988; 1989 (Box 3)
    - Macintosh Laboratory, 1984 (Box 3)
    - Mechanical Engineering and Applied Mechanics (MEAM) Laboratory, Erdal Emel, July 24, 1986 (Box 3)
  - Events Photographs, Slides, Contact Sheets, and Negatives (orange dot), 1985-1993
    - Air Space Show, 1991 (Box 3)
    - Business and Finance (RPM) Functional Analysis Presentation, June 10, 1993 (Box 3)
    - Check presentation, AT&T, Marie Howard, undated (Box 3)
    - Check presentation, GM, Chemical Engineering Faculty, March 3, 1986 (Box 3)
    - Engineering Administration Holiday Party, Food Shots, December 17, 1992 (Box 3)
    - Enginfest '87, Michigan Engineering, Mark Jaffe, April 22, 1987 (Box 3)
    - Farewell Reception, Department Chairmen, undated (Box 3)
    - Farewell Party, Duderstadt, March 30, 1986 (Box 3)
    - Farewell Reception, Charlie Fried, June 1991 (Box 3)
    - Farewell Reception, Jane Grigg, April 30, 1991 (Box 3)
    - Freshman Orientation, Michigan Engineer, August 15, 1987 (Box 3)
    - Graduation
      - Spring 1985 (Box 3)
      - May 3, 1986 (Box 3)
      - December 14, 1986 (Box 3)
      - May 2, 1987 (Box 4)
      - Honors Reception, Chrysler Center, December 20, 1987 (Box 4)
      - April 30, 1988 (Box 4)
      - Honors Reception, March 27, 1988 (Box 4)
      - Party, December 18, 1988 (Box 4)
      - Open House, North Campus Commons, December 18, 1988 (Box 4)
      - April 29, 1989 (Box 4)
      - Honors Reception, Spring 1989 (Box 4)
      - Winter 1989 (Box 4)
      - Open House, December 18, 1989 (Box 4)
    - Honors Assembly
      - December 11, 1986 (Box 4)
      - Dean's Office, March 23, 1986 (Box 4)
      - March 29, 1987 (Box 4)
      - Engineering, Amadeus Musicum Quartet, December 10, 1987 (Box 4)
      - December 10, 1987 (Box 4)
      - Holiday Assembly, Chrysler Center, December 8, 1988 (Box 4)
      - Dinner, 1989 (Box 4)
    - Martin Luther King Day Dinner, 1993 (Box 4)
    - New Faculty Picnic, Electrical Engineering and Computer Science (EECS), October 16, 1990 (Box 4)
    - Springfest, 1988 (Box 4)
    - St. George's Day, April 18, 1988 (Box 4)
    - St. George's Day, Spring 1989 (Box 4)
  - People Photographs, Slides, Contact Sheets, and Negatives (red dot), 1968-1993
    - College of Engineering (COE) Administration Portraits, January 31, 1992 (Box 4)
    - Cooley Contest Winners, March 21, 1988 (Box 4)
    - Cooley Contest Winners, March, 1989 (Box 4)
    - Atmospheric, Oceanic, and Space Sciences (AOSS) Faculty, undated (Box 4)
    - Chemical Engineering Faculty, 1986 (Box 4)
    - Naval Architecture and Marine Engineering (NAME) Faculty, undated (Box 4)
    - Methanol Car Team, late, 1980s (Box 4)
    - Engineering Administration Staff, 1990 (Box 4)
    - Engineering Administration Staff, October 28, 1991 (Box 4)
    - Staff, Nuclear Engineering, 1989 (Box 4)
    - Students, Chemical Engineering, May 9, 1986 (Box 4)
    - Atkin, Rich, undated (Box 4)
    - Brown, Michelle, May 1988 (Box 4)
    - Caldwell, Ed, April 1992 (Box 4)
    - Campbell, J.H., undated (Box 4)
    - Chen, Kan, September 13, 1971 (Box 4)
    - Chinatamaneni, Neil (student), undated. (Box 4)
    - Chmielewski, Eric, 1985 (Box 4)
    - Coe, Jerome T., undated (Box 4)
    - Coulter, K.E., undated (Box 4)
    - Earls, Julian, 1993 (Box 4)
    - Fernandez, undated (Box 4)
    - Galacia, Christina (student), 1992 (Box 4)
    - Greenleaf, Harry, undated (Box 4)
    - Hastings, Robert F., undated (Box 4)
    - Hannawalt, J., undated (Box 4)
    - Hodgson, Thom J., 1992 (Box 4)
    - Hose, Lelli, 1990 (Box 4)
    - Huff, Tom, undated (Box 4)
    - James, William, 1993 (Box 4)
    - Kirby, Brian (student), undated (Box 4)
    - Kirkby, R.C., 1977 (Box 4)
    - Kuzniewski, John, undated (Box 4)
    - Levy, Ben, 1968 (Box 4)
    - Marsh, Phil (Graduate student and research assistant), 1990 (Box 4)
    - Martin, J., undated (Box 4)
    - McLuhan, Marshall, 1977 (Box 4)
    - Miller, Martha (Counseling Office), undated (Box 4)
    - Miller, Ernest O., undated (Box 4)
    - Norland Frederic and Tom Kashangaki, undated (Box 4)
    - Norman, undated (Box 4)
    - Pahl, Kelli (Aerospace Engineer Senior), 1989 (Box 4)
    - Posduska, William, 1984 (Box 4)
    - Sartor, Gina (Women in Engineering Program), October 1993 (Box 4)
    - Schneider, Robert (Engineer Administration), 1991 (Box 4)
    - Severn, Peter (Glassblower), undated (Box 4)
    - Southerland, Karen and Jennifer Starrman, 1993 (Box 4)
    - Steding, H.R., undated (Box 4)
    - Van Wagoner, 1971 (Box 4)
    - Venturi, Bridget, undated (Box 4)
    - Wineman, Alan, undated (Box 4)
    - Weeby, Bethany, 1992 (Box 4)
    - Yeh, Curl, undated (Box 4)
  - Miscellaneous Coded Files, 1987-1994
    - "A Survey of Intellectual Activities", January 1987 (Box 4)
    - "Briefing for Regent Veronica L. Smith", February 26, 1988 (Box 4)
    - News about the University of Michigan College of Engineering
      - June 1993-November 10, 1993 (Box 4)
      - November 11, 1993-April 16, 1994 (Box 4)
      - April 18, 1994-August 30, 1994 (Box 4)
  - Various Photographs and Slides (purple dot), 1860-1993
    - General
      - 20th Anniversary Minority Engineering Programs Office Alumni Luncheon, 1989 (Box 9)
      - Aerospace Laboratories, undated (Box 9)
      - Aeronomy and Planetary Systems, undated (Box 9)
      - Airplane, N4291C, Aerial View Over Ann Arbor, undated (Box 9)
      - Airplane, Model Jet, undated (Box 9)
      - Alice Aycock Sculpture Groundbreaking, 1991 (Box 9)
      - Amoco Funded Microscope Lab Dedication, 1992 (Box 9)
      - Atmospheric, Oceanic and Space Sciences (AOSS) Lab, 1981 (Box 9)
      - Bioelectric Optics Computer Laboratory, undated (Box 9)
      - Camera, High Speed Nuclear, 1968 (Box 9)
      - Capital Campaign Kickoff Lunch, 1984 (Box 10)
      - Chemical Engineering, Display/Research Photographs, 1970 (Box 10)
      - Chemical Engineering Laboratories, 1970; undated (Box 10)
      - Chemical Engineering, circa 1960-1970 (Box 10)
      - Chen Chiang Visit, 1992 (Box 10)
      - Class of 1942 Plaza Dedication, 1992 (Box 10)
      - Clean Car Race, undated (Box 10)
      - CNC Milling Machine, undated (Box 10)
      - College of Engineering Staff Service Awards Reception, 1992 (Box 10)
      - Commencement, 1912 (Box 10)
      - Cyclotron, undated (Box 10)
      - Dean's Move to North Campus, 1982 (Box 10)
      - Dean Vest Farewell/ Christmas Party, 1988 (Box 10)
      - DeKaban Check/Gift Presentation, 1993 (Box 10)
      - Diversity Day, 1989 (Box 10)
      - E3 Camp, 1990 (Box 10)
      - Electrical Engineering and Computer Sciences (EECS) Building Groundbreaking; Governor James Blanchard and Dean James Duderstadt, 1984 (Box 10)
      - Electrical Engineering and Computer Science (EECS) Dedication; Senator Donald Riegle, 1986 (Box 10)
      - Electronic Blackboard, undated (Box 10)
      - Electronic Engine Tester, undated (Box 10)
      - Electronic Simulations, Aerospace, undated (Box 10)
      - Electron Physics Lab (Box 10)
      - Engineering 1-A Building, undated (Box 10)
      - Ergonomics Center, 1983 (Box 10)
      - Faculty Awards Dinner, 1989; 1992; 2 folders (Box 10)
      - Ford Gift to Engineering and Business Administration, 1989 (Box 10)
      - Ford Nuclear Reactor, undated (Box 10)
      - G-Factor Apparatus, undated (Box 10)
      - G.G. Brown Building Construction, undated (Box 10)
      - Graduation
        - Winter 1990 (Box 10)
        - President George Bush, Spring 1991 (Box 10)
        - Spring 1992 (Box 10)
      - Elaine Harden Farewell Reception, 1991 (Box 10)
      - High Altitude Engineering Laboratory, undated (Box 10)
      - Honors Dinner, 1990-1991; 2 folders (Box 10)
      - Industrial Technology Institute Building Model, undated (Box 10)
      - Interferometer, Propulsion Laboratory, Aerospace, undated (Box 10)
      - Interior of College of Engineering Buildings, undated (Box 10)
      - Industrial and Operations Engineering (IOE) Labs, undated (Box 10)
      - Electrical Engineering and Computer Science (EECS) Laboratories (Box 10)
      - Laboratory Images, undated (Box 10)
      - Laser Used for Study of Temperature Fluctuations, 1968 (Box 10)
      - Liquid Metals Laboratory, undated (Box 10)
      - Lockheed Pledge Presentation to Dean Vest, undated (Box 10)
      - Marathon Scholars, 1986 (Box 10)
      - Marine 2-Stroke Cycle Engine (Box 10)
      - Materials and Metallurgical Engineering, 1972-1973 (Box 10)
      - Meet Dean Banks Reception, 1992 (Box 10)
      - Mechanical and Metallurgical Laboratories (Box 10)
      - Minority Engineering Programs Office (MEPO), 1990-1991 (Box 10)
      - MEPO DAPCEP Program, 1991 (Box 10)
      - MEPO Willow Run/NASA Project, 1991 (Box 10)
      - METN, 1983 (Box 10)
      - MJMI; Dean Carrigan, Dean Banks and Professor Ulsoy, 1993 (Box 10)
      - Martin Luther King, Jr. Day, 1990-1992; 3 folders (Box 10)
      - Monroe Power Plant, 1972-1974 (Box 10)
      - Motion Pictures Through a Microscope of Chip Formation, undated (Box 10)
      - Naval Architecture and Marine Engineering (NAME) 100th Anniversary Banquet, 1981 (Box 10)
      - NAME Laboratories, undated (Box 10)
      - Neutron Spectrometer (Box 10)
      - North and South Colleges, 1962 (Box 10)
      - Observer Satellite Model, undated (Box 10)
      - Oceanography, undated (Box 10)
      - Outer space Model, undated (Box 10)
      - Patient Flow In Admitting System, undated (Box 10)
      - Pressure Tanks, undated (Box 10)
      - Project Stratum Satellite Model, undated (Box 10)
      - Prototype Hologram Projector, undated (Box 10)
      - Radiation Cave, undated (Box 10)
      - Research Photos, undated (Box 10)
      - Rockets
        - Nike-Apache Sounding, undated (Box 10)
        - Nike Tomahawk, 1968 (Box 10)
      - Satellite Model, undated (Box 10)
      - Society of Minority Engineering Students (SMES) Banquet, 1991 (Box 10)
      - Smog Chamber, undated (Box 10)
      - Society of Women Engineers (SWE), 1971 undated (Box 10)
      - Springfest, 1990-1992; 2 folders (Box 10)
      - Steam-Condensing Heat Transfer, undated (Box 10)
      - St. George's Day, 1991-1992; 2 folders (Box 10)
      - Student Recruiting Project, 1992 (Box 10)
      - Students, Miscellaneous, circa 1965-1985 (Box 10)
      - Summer Conference, 1968; undated (Box 10)
      - Tech Day, 1990-1991; 2 folders (Box 10)
      - Television, undated (Box 10)
      - Time Sharing Remote Computer Terminal, 1969 (Box 10)
      - USAEC Conference, 1967 (Box 10)
      - Vertical Evaporator, Chemical Engineering, undated (Box 10)
      - Willow Run Center, undated (Box 10)
      - Wind Tunnels